<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Project_items on arief koesdwiady</title><link>http://abkoesdw.github.io/project_items/</link><description>Recent content in Project_items on arief koesdwiady</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://abkoesdw.github.io/project_items/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reverse Osmosis Water Desalination Using Solar Energy</title><link>http://abkoesdw.github.io/project_items/ro/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://abkoesdw.github.io/project_items/ro/</guid><description>This is a joint project between KFUPM and MIT under Clean Water and Clean Energy Collaboration Center (CCWCE). The goal of the project is to desalinate water using Reverse Osmosis technology by efficiently utilizing solar energy. I developed the instrumentation and control systems as well as the Human Machine Interface (HMI) that are used to monitor and control the desalination process and solar tracking system.</description></item><item><title>Application of Machine Learning in Smart Mobility</title><link>http://abkoesdw.github.io/project_items/smart_mobility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://abkoesdw.github.io/project_items/smart_mobility/</guid><description>Transportation systems might be heavily affected by factors such as accidents and weather. Specifically, inclement weather conditions may have a drastic impact on travel time and traffic flow. This study has two objectives: first, to investigate a correlation between weather parameters and traffic flow and, second, to improve traffic flow prediction by proposing a novel holistic architecture.
It incorporates deep belief networks for traffic and weather prediction and decision-level data fusion scheme to enhance prediction accuracy using weather conditions.</description></item><item><title>Data-Driven Driver Distraction Detection</title><link>http://abkoesdw.github.io/project_items/distraction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://abkoesdw.github.io/project_items/distraction/</guid><description>In this project, we develop a data-driven driver distraction detection system, which consists of 3 major development stages:
Offline Multiview Classification Offline End-to-End Deep Learning Real-time End-to-End Deep Learning The ultimate goal is to detect when a driver is distracted, i.e., doing activity other than driving such as texting, talking on the phone, etc, so that we can provide appropriate warning to the driver to stop him/her from being distracted.</description></item><item><title>Event-Based Data Fusion using Dempster-Shaffer Theory</title><link>http://abkoesdw.github.io/project_items/ds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://abkoesdw.github.io/project_items/ds/</guid><description>In this project, we develop a technique to fuse asynchronous hard and soft data. We use the traffic prediction problem in a smart city as the case study. More specifically, we develop short-term traffic flow prediction approach that uses two types of data: streams of data, and event-based data.
In this work, Deep Belief Networks (DBNs) are used to independently predict traffic flow using streams of data, i.e., historical traffic flow and weather data, and event-based data, i.</description></item><item><title>GAN for Multi-Step Time Series Prediction</title><link>http://abkoesdw.github.io/project_items/multistep/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://abkoesdw.github.io/project_items/multistep/</guid><description>Multi-step time series prediction is known to suffer from increasing performance degradation the farther in the future the predictions are made. In this work, we introduce two approaches to address this weakness in recursive and multi-output prediction models.
One weakness of the recursive prediction is that it does not take into consideration the number of steps predicted by the model so far. The amount of correction the model needs to add differs from time-step to another along a multi-step prediction trajectory, since the deviation from ground truth is less acute in early steps.</description></item><item><title>Online Learning to Overcome Catastrophic Forgetting on Non-Stationary Time Series Prediction</title><link>http://abkoesdw.github.io/project_items/safe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://abkoesdw.github.io/project_items/safe/</guid><description>This work presents a practical approach for detecting non-stationarity in time series prediction. This method is called Spectral Evolution Analysis Feature Extraction (SAFE); it works by monitoring the evolution of the spectral contents of time series through a distance function.
This method is designed to work in combination with state-of-the-art machine learning methods in real time by informing the online predictors to perform necessary adaptation when a non-stationarity presents. We also propose an algorithm to proportionally include some past data in the adaption process to overcome the Catastrophic Forgetting problem.</description></item><item><title>Unmanned Aerial Vehicle Tracking Control</title><link>http://abkoesdw.github.io/project_items/uav/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://abkoesdw.github.io/project_items/uav/</guid><description>This project presents the application of a non-linear control technique, i.e., Invariance and Immersion (I&amp;amp;I), in trajectory tracking control, observer and adaptive control for quadrotor unmanned aerial vehicle (UAV).
I&amp;amp;I Trajectory Tracking Control This method was first introduced by Astolfi in 2003. The idea of this method is based on the system immersion and manifold invariance concepts. The main objective is to stabilize the system by immersing the plant dynamics into a target dynamic with a desired behavior.</description></item><item><title>USAD-2</title><link>http://abkoesdw.github.io/project_items/usad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://abkoesdw.github.io/project_items/usad/</guid><description>The USAD-2 is a project where we develop a unmanned ground vehicle for security applications. The vehicle is equipped with a 4-DOF robotic arm, a 2-DOF riffle, and 3 controlled cameras. I developed the instrumentation and control systems that are used to control the vehicle, robotic arm, cameras and the riffle remotely.</description></item></channel></rss>